middlesexbank.com 2004-12-04

# Middlesex Savings Bank

Consumer Privacy Policy Notice  
Internet Privacy Statement

**Middlesex Savings Bank  
Weathervane Insurance Agency, Inc.  
Weathervane Investment Services, Inc.**  

**About Our Privacy Policy**

Protecting your privacy is important to Middlesex Savings Bank, to Weathervane Investment Services, Inc. and Weathervane Insurance Agency, Inc. (our affiliates). The confidentiality and protection of customer information is one of our most fundamental responsibilities and your trust is one of our most important assets. Thus, the safekeeping of customer information is a priority for Middlesex Savings Bank our affiliated companies and our employees. 

We want you to understand what information we collect and how we use it. In order to provide our customers with a broad range of financial products and services as effectively and conveniently as possible, we use technology to manage and maintain customer information. 

The following policy serves as a standard for all Middlesex Savings Bank and its affiliated companies’ employees for the collection, use, retention, and security of nonpublic personal information. 

We encourage you to read the following Consumer Privacy Policy Notice to fully understand our commitment to protecting your privacy. Customers of Middlesex Savings Bank can expect to receive a written copy of this policy annually. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact our Information Center at 1-877-463-6287. 

* * *

**Consumer Privacy Policy Notice**

At Middlesex Savings Bank and our affiliated companies, we value and respect the trust placed in us by our customers. For this reason, we want you to know how we deal with customer information and privacy. 

**Information We Collect:**

We collect, use, and retain information about you only where we reasonably believe that it will help administer our business or provide valuable products, services, and other opportunities to you. We collect and retain information about you only for specific business purposes. We use information to administer your records, accounts, and funds; to comply with certain laws and regulations; to protect your accounts from fraud and misuse; and to understand your financial needs so that we can provide you with quality products and superior service. 

We collect personal and financial information about you from the following sources: 

  * Information we receive from you on applications and other forms (such as your name, address, social security number, assets, liabilities and income) 
  * Information about your transactions with us (such as your account balance, payment history, and parties to transactions) 
  * Information we receive from consumer reporting agencies (such as your credit history and creditworthiness) 

**Disclosure of Information:**

We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law. It is our policy not to reveal specific information about customer accounts or other personally identifiable data to unaffiliated third parties for their independent use. We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to nonaffiliated third parties that perform administrative, processing and other account services, to companies that market financial products and services on our behalf, and as otherwise required or permitted by law. The Bank and its affiliated companies are permitted under law to share with each other information about our experiences or transactions with you or your account (such as your account balance and your payment history with us). 

We also may share additional information about you or your account (such as information we receive from you in applications and information from credit reporting agencies) with our affiliates. You may direct us not to disclose information between the Bank and our affiliates that does not relate solely to experiences or transactions with you or your account (such as application information and credit bureau information) by writing to us at P.O. Box 358, Natick, MA, 01760 or by calling us at 1-877-INFO CTR (1-877-463-6287). If you make such a request, it will apply to all of your consumer relationships within the Middlesex Savings Bank family of affiliated companies. 

**You do not need to notify us more than once if you have multiple accounts, or if you have previously notified us.**

If you have a joint account, a request by one party will apply to the entire account. Your request will be processed within four weeks of receipt. You may still receive offers with your account statements, when you visit or contact us in connection with the maintenance and servicing of your account. 

**Business Relationships With Third Parties:**

When the Bank and our affiliates conduct business with vendors and suppliers, we require those vendors to maintain similar standards of conduct regarding the privacy of customer information that is provided to them. 

**Protection and Confidentiality of Information:**

Middlesex Savings Bank and our affiliated companies are committed to the security of your information. All of our operational and data processing systems are located in secure environments that protect your information from being accessed by unauthorized third parties. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with regulatory standards to protect your information. 

**Maintenance of Account Information:**

We continually strive to maintain complete and accurate information about you and your accounts. If you believe that our records contain inaccurate or incomplete information about you, please notify us. We will investigate your concerns and correct any inaccuracies as quickly as possible. 

**Limitations on Employee Access:**

Access to customer information is limited to employees with a business reason to know such information. Employees are educated on the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of customer information. All Bank and affiliate employees are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of customer information. Any employee who violates these principles is subject to disciplinary action.>

**Inquiries:**

Customers who have questions about this policy or have a question about the privacy of their information are invited to speak with a representative at a local branch, call us at 1-877-463-6287 or e-mail us at [info@middlesexbank.com](mailto:info@middlesexbank.com)

**Additional Information:**

You can help protect your privacy by following these simple suggestions: 

  * Never give out your Social Security Number or personal credit information over the telephone unless you initiate the call. 
  * Tear up or shred unwanted ATM receipts, bank statements, and credit card offers. 
  * Review your monthly statements for unauthorized activity. If a statement or loan bill is missing, notify the bank immediately. 
  * Keep your PIN and other passwords secure and change them periodically. 

You can write to the following agencies to reduce the amount of advertising you receive from other companies. Include the name, address and telephone number(s) you want removed from their lists. 

**Mail Preference Service**  
c/o Direct Marketing Association  
P.O. Box 9008  
Farmington, NY 11735-9008 

**Telephone Preference Service**  
c/o Direct Marketing Association  
P.O. Box 9014  
Farmington, NY 11735-9014 

You can request to be removed from pre-approved credit solicitations by writing to the following credit reporting agencies. You will need to provide your name, address and social security number. 

**Equifax, Inc.**  
Options  
P.O. Box 740123  
Atlanta, GA 30374-0123 

**Experian**  
Consumer Opt-Out  
P.O. Box 919  
Allen, TX 75013 

**Trans Union Corporation**  
Name Removal Option  
P.O. Box 97328  
Jackson, MS 39288-7328  

* * *

**Internet Privacy Statement**

Visitors to our web site remain anonymous. We do not collect identifying information about visitors to our site. We may use standard software to collect non-identifying information about our visitors, such as: 

  * Date and time our site was accessed 
  * IP address (A numeric address given to servers connected to the Internet) 
  * Web browser used 
  * City, state, and country 

Middlesex Savings Bank may use this information to create summary statistics and to determine the level of interest in information available on our site. 

Visitors may elect to provide us with personal information via E-mail, online registration forms, or our guest book. This information is used internally, as appropriate, to handle the sender's request. It is not disseminated or sold to other organizations. 

Some areas of our web site may use a "cookie" temporarily stored in the visitor's computer memory (RAM) to allow the web server to log the pages you use within the site and to know if you have visited the site before. 

Please be aware that our Privacy Statement only applies while you are at Middlesex Savings Bank's web site, and does not apply if you leave our web site by following any links we may have provided for your convenience, or by using the search engine provided on our home page.
